KYLE RASSWEILER

Chone: +1-613-724-9141 | ■ Email: jobs@kylerassweiler.ca

♠ Portfolio: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca | ♠ Github: www.github.com/rassweiler

(<u>b</u>) Code Camp: https://www.freecodecamp.org/kylerassweiler

Summary

Engineering Specialist with experience in: software development, networking, programmable logic controllers, robotics, electronics, and machining.

Skills

Software	Angular, Apache2 , Assembly(PIC), C++, CMake, Django, Git, H	ITML,
	JavaScript, Meteor, Mongoose, Node, PHP, Python, React, Redu	X

Virtualisation

Virtual Box, Qemu/KVM, Docker, XCP-NG

Systems

BSD, Arch, Debian, Windows, Proxmox

Hardware AB(Micro800), Arduino, Mitsubishi, Omron, Raspberry Pi, Toyopuc, Zigbee

Projects

KRello A simple Trello clone developed using react and redux with jest and

enzyme for testing.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/krello/

Demo: https://krello.kylerassweiler.com/
Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/krello

KR-Display A responsive Meteor application for the display of SQL data. The system

uses jobs to schedule information updates from the SQL server, the jobs

then update the local MongoDB database.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/kr-display/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kr-display

Kawasaki AS Parser A Kawasaki robot backup parser written in TypeScript for browser or

Node. The library also includes TypeScript interfaces for use in new

projects.

Website: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/kawasaki-parser/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kawasaki-as-parser

Robot Project Utility

Mk2

A simple utility written in JS, HTML, CSS, React, and Electron(Node.js). The utility allows the user to view robot backup information from various robot brands(Currently Kawasaki), and is also used to compare two backups then determine any change points. The utility can also be used for work planning.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/robot-project-

<u>utility/</u>

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/robot-project-utility

Experience

Engineering Specialist

2017 - Present

TEMA (Toyota)

PLC programming, Robotic Vision (Robeye system), 3D Factory Design, Robot programming, Electrical system troubleshooting, Improving processes and designs, Work planning, Commissioning, Equipment buy offs, Vendor support, Laser Welding, Friction Stir Welding, Aluminium Spot Welding

Robotics Technician

2014 - 2017

FIO Automotive

PLC programming, Robot programming, Machining, Electrical system wiring,

Electronics repairing, Robot repairing, Weld condition setup and

modification, Setup SCADA system and PLC networking.

Operational Technician

Repair equipment, Preventative Maintenance, Inspections.

2012 - 2014

Abbott Point Of Care

Education

Software Certificates

Free Code Camp

2022 -

Electro-Mechanical Engineering Technician Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON.

2010 - 2012

Computer Animation

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON.

2007 - 2010